<arrakis>
    <dune2000>
        <item>
            <title>Ultimate Guide To Dune (Part 1) The Introduction</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Ultimate Guide To Dune (Part 1) The Introduction</title>
                <summary>The guide to the greatest Sci-Fi series ever written. Frank Herbert's Masterpiece spans over the course of five thousand years, contains dozens of main characters, and explores the human condition in a way that no novels before have nor likely ever will with this passion.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/1NZiTVPXmNM</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Ultimate Guide To Dune (Part 2) Book One</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Ultimate Guide To Dune (Part 2) Book One</title>
                <summary>In this part, we will explore the first novel in Frank Herbert's epic science fiction series. The Bene Gesserit and their schemes, The Noble House Atreides vs the Vile Harkonnens, Will Paul become the Kwisatz Haderach?</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/5ga4PYMKwQ0</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Ultimate Guide to Dune (Part 3) Book Two</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Ultimate Guide to Dune (Part 3) Book Two</title>
                <summary>Each novel in the Saga preceding Dune deals with the effects of Paul’s Legacy on the Known universe, Dune Messiah and Children of Dune most of all. At the Start of Messiah, we are immediately faced with problems surrounding Pauls Rule of the Imperium. Dune Messiah opens with a recorded interrogation between a Fremen priest and a historian named Bronso, who has been labelled a “heretic” and sentenced to death, for his accurate writings on emperor Paul Muad’Dib. 12 years have passed since the events of Dune. At this point it time, Paul Atreides rules from Arrakis as Emperor of the Imperium. Though Paul is the most powerful Emperor ever, he is still incapable of stopping the lethal religious excesses of the juggernaut he has created.The Jihad has been unleashed at it has conquered most of the known universe. 61 billion people have died so far due to Paul’s decision to become the messiah of the Fremen people. But according to Paul’s vision this nowhere close to the worst possible outcome for humanity. It is in Dune Messiah that Paul begins the Golden Path. A complex and perilous plan to set humanity on a course that will not lead to its eventual stagnation and extinction, at the same time Paul must balance this with his duties as the ruler of the Galactic Empire and the Center of the Fremen religion.

At the same time, the outlying powers in the universe are growing restless with the new status quo. Several forces are at work and conspire together to undo Paul Atreides and reverse the events that lead to his ascension to the throne, these forces include the Bene Gesserit, who are vexed that they have lost control of their kwisatz haderach, the remnants of the displaced House Corrino, the former occupants of the throne, the spacing guild who are now under pauls control due to his control over the spice, and the Bene Tleilax, who have their own agenda, the tleilaxu have sent the Face Dance Scytale as their representative.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/MLJuIO0plWk</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dune: What Happened To Earth?</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Dune: What Happened To Earth?</title>
                <summary>The original Dune Saga takes place over 20,000 years in our future, Earth is mentioned only a handful of times. According to Appendix II Religion of dune, the Commission of Ecumenical Translators communed on what is referred to as old earth, which was considered a neutral territory.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/NXZJ1FxK2-M</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Tleilaxu of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Tleilaxu of Dune</title>
                <summary>An exploration of the ultimate xenophobes of the Dune universe. Spoilers on!</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/kS746z41Mw4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Spacing Guild of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Spacing Guild of Dune</title>
                <summary>In the Dune universe, the spacing Guild possesses exclusive access to faster-than-light space travel. Through the use of a special craft known as a Highliner, The Guild obtains these speeds thanks to the Holtzman Effect, a phenomenon which is related to the repellant force of quantum entities. The ability to fold space is granted by the Holtzman engine, and it allows for instantaneous travel from one side of the universe to the other. Guild Highlanders are usually of enormous size thus they allow for thousands to be transported at once, they could also easily transport planetary goods such as large amounts of the spice melange. The Spacing Guild is an impartial transporter. Persons may use their services for commerce, war or missions of mercy with the same assurance of safety and anonymity.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/V4xlpAMuce8</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Ixian Technocracy of Dune + Dune Messiah Preview</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Ixian Technocracy of Dune + Dune Messiah Preview</title>
                <summary>In Frank Herbert’s Dune Saga, Ix is the 9th planet in the Alkalurops star system, The Ixian Technocracy maintains supreme control over the world. The planet derives its name from the Roman numeral (IX 9) which marks it as the 9th planet. The Ixian economy relies on the manufacturing of complex machinery which on occasion broke the restrictions set in place by the Butlerian Jihad, which stated that no machine could be created which imitated the human mind. Though the Ixians often pushed or broke the ban on artificial intelligence, desire for Ixian products throughout the Imperium mostly keeps them one step ahead of invasion by the great houses. Ix is the leading provider of technology in all the known imperium, and Ixian devices are commonplace and considered essential throughout the series.

Technocracy: the government or control of society or industry by an elite of technical experts.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/en3px5RLmZ4</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Bene Gesserit of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Bene Gesserit of Dune</title>
                <summary>Just sharing my ideas one of my favorite book series, A Song of Ice and Fire by George RR Martin. This video may contain spoilers for those of you who are not up to date with the series. That goes for the HBO show and the books.

I'm just speculating and guessing on some ideas that I have on how future events will transpire in the series. Keep in mind however, I know nothing. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/pbr_jGlNe0I</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dune: A Brief History of Space Travel</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Dune: A Brief History of Space Travel</title>
                <summary>In the Dune universe, the Holtzman effect is a scientific theory that relates to the repellent force of particles on a subatomic level. Its discovery would lead to many advancements in technology in the Dune universe. Glow Globes Spencer's the Holtzman Shield and the most significant space travel. Using the Holtzman engine grants the ability to fold space and allows instantaneous space travel from one place in the universe to another. 

Space travel is extremely important in the evolution of humanity, it has allowed them to populate throughout the known universe. For thousands of years, the spacing Guild maintained a monopoly on space travel, and their process was extremely expensive. Their pilots were the only ones who could navigate through space, using prescience brought on by extreme amounts of the spice melange. Without them, the extraordinarily complex mathematics involved in producing reliable physical projections of such events would only be possible with thinking machines, which were prohibited by the Butlerian Jihad.

It can be assumed that at least some understood that eventually, the guilds monopoly on space travel would end. The fringe worlds were always pushing the boundaries of their technologies. This is suggested as early as Children of Dune. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/-bX4EuYwDKI</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Sandworms of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Sandworms of Dune</title>
                <summary>Just sharing my ideas one of my favorite book series, A Song of Ice and Fire by George RR Martin. This video may contain spoilers for those of you who are not up to date with the series. That goes for the HBO show and the books.

I'm just speculating and guessing on some ideas that I have on how future events will transpire in the series. Keep in mind however, I know nothing. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/T52SL4TFWpU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Mentat of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Mentat of Dune</title>
                <summary>The mentat are the human computers of the Dune universe. The discipline was developed as a way to replace thinking machines which had been outlawed following the Butlerian Jihad. Well Known mentats in the Dune universe include Thufir Hawat, who spent many years employed by house Atreides and Hayt, whose name is the Arabic word حياة meaning “Life”, the Duncan Idaho Ghola who first appears in Dune Messiah. Of course the most famous mentat of all is Paul Atreides himself.

Strict mental conditioning is required to produce a mentat, a certain level of mental capacity is also necessary. Mentats are often employed by the great houses of the Imperium. Though was some mentats possess greater abilities then others typically all of them were guaranteed employment somewhere. The potential to become a mentat was something that very few possessed. </summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/g-eDSZMYt7o</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>The Fremen of Dune | Deep Exploration | Arabic Origins</title>
            <meta>
                <title>The Fremen of Dune | Deep Exploration | Arabic Origins</title>
                <summary>The Fremen were the fictional humans, who considered the planet Arrakis their home. They formed a crucial part in the establishment of the Atreides Empire and Muad'Dib's Jihad launched by Paul Atreides.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/tJuDZd5T-cw</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Honored Matres of Dune</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Honored Matres of Dune</title>
                <summary>In the great scattering which took place after the death of the Worm God Emperor, the Bene Gesserit sisterhood sent out several colonization teams of their own, to explore the further reaches of space. These groups were never heard from again. 1,500 hundred years after the scattering it was discovered that some did survive, and in fact thrived, in great numbers and power. But they were no longer like the sister of the old empire. The scattering brought the necessity for key changes in their beliefs, objectives, and customs. The ways of the fish speakers, The Servants of the God-Emperor have mingled with the ways of the Bene Gesserit, creating the Honored Matres.

Though many of the Bene Gesserit ways remained to the Honored Matres, they also possessed outside ideologies and philosophies that make them significantly different from their ancestral origins. While the Bene Gesserit Sisterhood used subtle and deceptive methods to retain and maintain their power within an existing balance of power, the Matres sought absolute domination of all other groups. As such their strategy required either the enslavement or the destruction of all other power brokers, this also demanded that the matres possess powerful control mechanisms. 

The most effective method used by the Honored Matres to infiltrate and overwhelm other groups was a form of "sexual enslavement." During their evolution in uncharted space, they perfected sexual intercourse into a narcotic process. By using carefully crafted skills, an Honored Matre learned how to coerce an outsider – typically a male – into total subservience. This action, performed often, and upon the right individuals, allowed them to conquer many other groups in the scattering, as a result, they were able to build a formidable military and resource base</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/n9pXYWQ3fhE</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dune: C.H.O.A.M. & Rise of the Empire</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Dune: C.H.O.A.M. & Rise of the Empire</title>
                <summary>In the Dune universe, CHOAM is the largest single source of wealth in the universe. The Combine Honnete Ober Advancer Mercantiles, abbreviated as CHOAM controls all economic affairs across the universe. Choam like everyone else relies upon the spacing guild for faster than light transport. Choam touched nearly every product moved by the guild from technology to the spice melange. Many of the great and minor houses depended upon the profits of Choam, and an enormous portion of those profits depended upon the most valued commodity in the universe, the spice Melange, which extended life, heightened awareness and was necessary to space travel.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/aSc8hpQMtmg</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>

        <item>
            <title>Dune: Jacurutu and the Cast Out</title>
            <meta>
                <title>Dune: Jacurutu and the Cast Out</title>
                <summary>Long before the days of house Atreides on Arrakis, before Liet Kynes, and before the rule of Shaddam IV, there were certain tribes that roamed the desert known as water hunters. The Fremen called them Iduali, “water insects”. They would steal the water of fremen they caught in the desert, even the water of the body. The Sietch they lived in was called Jacurutu. And it was in Jacurutu that the other fremen tribes banded to get to destroy the Iduali. The place was considered Tabu after that, and from that day forth no fremen had gone to Jacurutu, its very location was lost. The remaining Iduali according to legend were Cast Out from fremen society.</summary>
            </meta>
            <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch/yYHONxeITXU</link>
            <thumbnail>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/muaddibttv/artwork/master/arrakis/dune2000.png</thumbnail>
        </item>
    </dune2000>
</arrakis>